ILGWU. Los Angeles Joint Board photographs 5780/046 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Hubert Humphrey, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Mrs. Humphrey during Mr. Humphrey's campaign Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff26
- ILGWU Mobile Health Unit presentation with Cesar Chavez (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff27
- Imports Rally, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff28
- Lyndon B. Johnson for President Campaign (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff29
- Judy Bond Strike, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff30
- Lou-Gene Strike (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff31
- Otto- Vice President Sam Otto Retirement Party (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff32
- President Sol Chaiken and wife at 75th Anniversary of the ILGWU in Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff33
- President Louis Stulberg and members of the G.E.B. Committee visiting Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  December 1971 Collection re- boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff34
- President Louis Stulberg visiting Los Angeles, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff35
- Roosevelt for Governor, Los Angeles, CA (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff36
- Tabak, Inc. Strike, Lock-out (Box 4, Folder 21)
  1968 Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff37
- Tunney for U.S. Senator Campaign (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff38
- Union Label. First union label in California; Union label fashion show (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff39
- Vice President Glenn Clay visiting Los Angeles during the Coat and Suit negotiations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff40
- Western States Region Seminar, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff41
- Miscellaneous, duplicates, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Vice President Wall and President Lois Stulberg; Local 482 Executive Board; Vice President Wall testimonial being congratulated by Major Bradley; California State federation, COPE Convention. Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff42
- Miscellaneous., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Wedding of Southern California Davis Pleating member at Union headquarters, 1978; various conferences, dinner events, meetings- no descriptions Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff43
- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 28)
  No descriptions Collection re-boxed, this was formerly box 2, ff44